Could I have a moment, Lady Elfaria?
Wake up.
That hurts, Sarissa.
Then, please act in a way
befitting a Magia Vander.
You're always sleeping or looking
at the bottom of the Tower.
You frivolous Magia Vander
in saint clothing.
What do you want?
Please take a moment to review these.
These are the candidates
recommended by our scouts.
Candidates?
Yes. We have a nice harvest this year.
And that one seems like an excellent
candidate for the Ice Faction.
Julius Reinberg.
He's making a performance
at the festival as we speak.
He may suited to become
your successor, Lady Elfaria.
Indeed, if he's as good as reported here,
he may be able to become my successor.
Are you afraid of opening
your eyes again?
Do you hate being like
a stranger to yourself?
Even if you realize you have no talent
Does that become a pretext
to keep running away?
To respond to the screams
echoing within
Who is there to answer them?
At least, in the few moments
of your life
I want you to be an honest actor
What if today is that day?
Are you afraid of opening
your eyes again?
Do you hate being like
a stranger to yourself?
But you've realized, haven't you?
Your body can't stop moving
"If I think of you, who I can't bear to lose,
my fears seem trivial."
Even if I expose my life and sing
In time, you will understand
Will it end here?
You wouldn't want that, would you?
(Episode 7: El Glace Frosse)
Crown Attack has reached the finale!
Whoever claims the crown on the podium
will get the glory!
And right now, all three members of Squad 9
will face up against Will of Squad 6!
I'm glad you made it, Flunkee.
I was worried that we would win
just like this.
If I didn't crush you
without humiliating you,
I wouldn't be satisfied.
Don't worry, Julius.
I don't plan on losing before
you apologize to Donnan and others.
That's big talk for a no-talent.
From now on, you're nothing more
than a little rat for me to toy with.
A smokescreen?
I can sense their magic in there.
Are they going to fire their spells?
No.
Footsteps.
They're moving.
They're trying to surround me.
If I don't keep moving, they'll get me.
Even if my view is blocked,
I can detect where their spells come from.
There's the second attack,
and the third attack.
I dodged all three of them,
now I know where they are.
I got you!
A fourth one?!
What are you doing, Flunkee?
We haven't even moved one step.
Hey, look at that!
There are four, no, five Julius?
Illusion? No, that's not it.
Could it be...
I forgot to mention it.
That me over there explodes, you know?
Eisplosion.
Will!
Will is frozen after getting caught in
a sudden explosion from that Julius!
But rather than that, what was that?
That spell...
There's no doubt about it.
The secret magic invented
by the prodigy Elfaria.
El Glace Frosse.
As a great feat in creating
twelve original spells,
Elfaria has a serial art named after her
in recognition of this achievement.
And he's using one of the spells
from that series.
El One: Ars Weiss.
A clone spell that creates living
ice sculptures of the caster.
How can you use Elfie's spell?
Because I'm talented.
What other answer do you need?
I learned how to use this spell
all on my own.
It may only be the first of the series,
but I've reached the Magia Vander.
I guess Albis Vina
isn't so special after all.
Someday, I'll strip her of everything.
Julius!
I can move my clones as I wish
and have them cast spells as well.
What's wrong, No-talent?
If you stay still like that,
you're going to lose to them!
And...
What's this?
The attacks stopped?
I can even make a cage like this.
Remote circle?
He made a barrier using his clones
as the anchor.
I'm trapped.
Nothing's easier than hunting
a wild animal on a rampage.
Xelunea Caulis.
It's over.
So, so...
So strong!
He's too strong!
Win the battle without moving.
It's the ideal of any mage.
Julius Reinberg.
It's no wonder that he's able to
earn over 10,000 credits.
Are you watching, scouts?
As you can see, I've flawlessly
mastered Albis Vina's secret ice magic.
I, Julius Reinberg, will be
the successor to Lady Elfaria.
He can use Lady Elfaria's spell.
That's incredible.
Nobody can beat him.
It's all a demonstration.
He took advantage of Will's monster-like
agility to make himself look good.
How clever.
However...
He'll look silly if he loses here.
Wait, it couldn't be...
How did he break free?
Thank you, Julius.
Your spell helped me to cool my head.
I tend to get worked up when it comes
to Elfie, it's a bad habit of mine.
What are you babbling about?
This time, I'll disgrace you for sure!
First of all,
your Ars Weiss isn't perfect.
He hid himself in the first attack,
and then launched his attack
from their blind spot.
Like he did to me.
What was that?!
Will took out two members of Squad 9!
What's going on?!
Look at that.
Julius's clones are falling apart.
You had your friends to help
you control the clones
and were able to cast
Elfie's spell for a moment.
You're not even close to her level.
Damn you!
Julius Reinberg.
Indeed, if he's as good as reported here,
he may be able to become my successor.
But, Sarissa, what I want
isn't a successor.
What I want by my side is a sword.
Your Ars Weiss isn't perfect.
Unlike the autonomous guardians,
Ars Weiss is controlled
completely by the caster.
Your teammates were helping you
control your clones.
You haven't mastered Ars Weiss.
A no-talent who can't even use magic...
Don't you dare lecture me!
I'll freeze your big mouth!
I hate to admit it.
I'm not good enough to control
four clones at once yet.
Without their support,
this spell will drain me fast.
But!
He will never know
which one is the real me.
My clones are just as beautiful as I am.
They match my good looks
and handsomeness.
The disguise is flawless.
There's no way he can tell us apart-
Frall!
How did you know?
The average body temperature of an Ars Weiss
clone is the exact opposite of the caster's.
It's around minus 36 or 37 degrees.
It can be even lower
depending on how it is cast.
If the caster isn't completely in control,
the cold will seep out of the clones.
Just like with Frost Walkers,
ice crystals form around their feet.
Just how?
How could a no-talent like you
know more about this spell than I do?
Tell me!
Because Elfie...
Elfaria was my childhood friend.
We were both abandoned and
we grew up in the same orphanage.
So I know a lot about Elfaria's magic.
I admired it, that's why I studied it.
But I could never reach her.
Don't worry.
Our memories and your hard work
would never go in vain.
That's why, Julius...
I know all the strengths and
weaknesses of Elfie's magic.
That's impossible!
This is Albis Vina's!
Magia Vander's secret magic!
I won't let a no-talent like you mock it!
Julius, you sure are amazing.
No mage has ever been able to
use her magic before.
But...
Ars Weiss is a spell that Elfie created
when she was two years old.
What? Two years old?
So it's not perfect and it can be beaten.
Using that to brag would make you
nothing more than the Naked King!
The Naked King?
Who? Me?
Rather than that...
Two years old?
She was an infant.
I was so proud of myself for
learning this spell.
But I'm no better than an infant?
Don't screw with me!
Wow, look at that!
There are more clones!
Five, six, seven...
There are eight Julius!
Did you think four was my limit?
Don't underestimate me!
It doesn't matter if
I can't control them perfectly.
I'll beat you with sheer numbers.
This time, it's your loss!
Sorry, Julius.
I used to get bullied by ten Elfie.
Glace Itier!
Stop him!
Wait!
Will wins against Julius!
What a twist! A no-talent has just beaten
an elite with more than 10,000 credits!
Senior Will!
Will!
Will Serfort.
It's hard to believe, but there's
nothing that stands in his way.
All he has to do is to get the crown.
Good grief.
Do you even know how this game works?
While you two were busy dueling,
I went ahead and picked this up.
How long have they been there?!
The twists just keep on coming!
The winner of Crown Attack is...
Squad 12, led by Wignall Lindor!
It seems the Crown Attack has ended.
Sarissa.
Is there a spell that lets you
go back to the past?
There is no such spell.
How about a spell to erase a memory?
There may be one among
the forbidden arts,
but I would not allow you to use it.
You're wrong, Will!
I wasn't bullying you!
I just wanted you all to myself
so we could play together all the time!
Now all the students know
about my dark past.
That flunkee is even able to win
against Julius.
I will definitely defeat you.
Will!
I'm sorry. They took it.
But I'm able to fulfill the promise.
Peering through the telescope
I gaze at you
The everyday life I see there
is completely upside down
I can't keep my feet on the ground
My heart is in the clouds
Feelings with no destination
will only lead to pain
Ah, it's so cruel
The spell "what if" has no effect
But everything would be fine
if it were with me
I can't help but think of that
I used to be able to say,
"I love you. Do you love me? I love you!"
It was like half-eaten frozen,
crunchy memories
(We're stuck in Love)
Not enough, not enough, not enough
There's not enough of you
(We're stuck in Love)
I want to touch you, I want to touch you
It's so cold
Before love freezes over
Warm it up, please
Next up, Episode 8 of
Wistoria: Wand and Sword,
"Shall we date?"